战争要来临了
There is a war coming.
可怕的战争
A-a terrible war.
到时会一片混乱
There-there will be chaos.
街上血流成河
Rivers of blood in the streets.
我知道的
I know it!
我能预见到
I-I can see it coming.
是时候了
It's time.
总得有人接替他  那不如就让我来
Somebody has to take over; it might as well be me.
我叫詹姆斯・戈登  我是一名警探
My name's James Gordon. I'm a detective.
我会找到凶手的
I will find the man who did this.
佩珀是被菲什・穆尼和警察陷害的
Pepper was framed by Fish Mooney and the cops.
詹姆斯・戈登不是一个好人
James Gordon is not a good guy.
你该拥有更好的人
You deserve better.
再也别回哥谭了
Don't ever come back to Gotham.
科波特死前  我和他谈过
I spoke with Cobblepot before he died.
人之将死  其言也善
Men who are about to die are very honest.
我会杀了那个老头子
I am going to kill that old man.
我真希望那个小企鹅还活着
I just wish Penguin was still alive.
我一直在观察你
I've been watching you.
我看到杀死韦恩夫妇的真凶了
I saw who really killed the Waynes.
本字幕由 YYeTs 人人影视 原创翻译
[WEB&BD版美剧字幕精编者]再加工制作
本人由衷感谢原译作者的无私奉献  并保留所有译作者的信息
如需其它剧集字幕  请登陆新浪微博（http://weibo.com/MJZM100）
或发邮件索取 lj20090303@163.com
翻译：eginamoon   艾瑞卡   木浅薰   Silence   charcie
借过
Excuse me!
翻译：哥谭直属   DustD   迷失_绽放   草草
时间轴：最可爱的小胖子   Kallen   讷讷       后期：饿得慌
谢谢
Thank you.
有人偷了...拦住他
Somebody took... Stop him!
您需要...
You need some...?
回家了
Home.
直播一则爆炸性新闻...
And let's go live for some breaking news...
谢谢你  杰森
Thank you, Jason.
正在为您播报冲击了
I'm coming to you with the latest wrinkle in a story
哥谭金融界事件的最新消息
that sent shockwaves through the financial world of Gotham.
我正站在罗纳德・丹泽尔家门前
I'm standing before the home of Ronald Danzer,
据报道  他在一个巨大的庞氏骗局中
the man who bilked investors out of a reported half billion dollars
骗走了投资人五亿美元
in a vast Ponzi scheme.
丹泽尔被保释了  目前正在等候审判
Danzer is currently out on bail awaiting trial.
所有人  法官  陪审团  地检官
All of them-- the judge, the jury, the D.A.--
他们要什么就给什么
pay them whatever it takes.
我才不要为了几个
I am not going to prison just because
丢了养老金的蠢巴士司机和傻老太太进监狱呢
a few dumb bus drivers and stupid old ladies lost their damn pensions.
我得偷偷溜出去
I got to sneak out.
村民拿着草耙堵在这儿呢
The villagers are here with pitchforks.
你是我的律师
You're my lawyer.
搞定这事
Fix this!
卖气球咯
Balloons!
Balloon...!
卖气球咯
Here, balloons!
要来个气球吗
Want a balloon?
什么  不  谢谢你  不用了
What? No. No, thank you. No.
罗纳德・丹泽尔吗
Ronald Danzer?
你是谁
Who are you?
特效：宝宝        校对&总监：草草
救救我
Help me!
那是罗纳德・丹泽尔  打开摄像机
That's Ronald Danzer. Roll the camera!
开始拍摄
Roll the camera!
救救我
Help me...!
事情出现了诡异的转折
In a bizarre turn of events,
一个貌似是罗纳德・丹泽尔的人
a man appearing to be Ronald Danzer
正缓缓升上哥谭的天空
is rising into the air above Gotham,
他被绑在了...
attached to...
一个气象气球上
a weather balloon.
哥谭
第一季第三集
推车里面装满了增重用的砖头
Cart was loaded with bricks for ballast.
罗纳德・丹泽尔
So, Ronald Danzer
把半数哥谭市民的存款骗了个精光
cheats half of Gotham out of their savings,
但他还没接受审判
but before he can stand trial,
就被不明嫌犯拴在气球上飞走了
an unknown man clips him to a balloon?
都没有尸体
No body?
我们要认定为凶杀吗
We calling this a murder?
这叫为民除害
Call it a public service.
丹泽尔是个人渣  他罪有应得
Danzer was a bum. He got what he deserved.
我要去吃个丹麦酥
I'm gonna go get a Danish.
这是我应得的
It's what I deserve.
该死
Damn it!
给我把奥布莱恩找来
Somebody find me O'Brian!
再拿点冰块来
And get me some ice!
是  警督
Yes, sir, Lieutenant.
你是谁
Who the hell are you?
吉姆・戈登
Jim Gordon.
吉姆・戈登  你是布洛克的新搭档  是吧
Jim Gordon. You're Bullock's new partner, hey?
就是你  我是比尔・克兰斯顿警督
Yeah. Lieutenant Bill Cranston.
布洛克告诉我你特别正直
Yeah, Bullock tells me you're a real Boy Scout.
觉得我们不该采取这种手段吗
Don't think we should be roughing up the skels?
他们的确有人权啊
Well, they do have their rights.
我得记住这一点
I'm gonna have to remember that.
或许回头把这话纹在屁股上
Maybe I'll get that tattooed on my ass.
我给你看样东西  戈登
Let me show you something, Gordon.
这是哥谭商会给我们的礼物
This was a gift from the Gotham Chamber of Commerce
感谢我们多年来尽忠职守
for years of service.
我管他叫奥布莱恩
I call him O'Brian.
他恰好是警局最好的审讯官
He also just happens to be the best interrogator on the force.
很高兴认识你  戈登
Nice meeting you, Gordon.
卢克  跟奥布莱恩警长问好
Oh, Luke, say hello to Sergeant O'Brian.
禁止入内
不  不要
No! No!
我刚刚见过了克兰斯顿警督
I just met Lieutenant Cranston.
伟人  神话  传说
The man, the myth, the legend.
他就是个恶棍
He's a thug.
没有指纹
So, no fingerprints,
小推车又太容易买到或盗取  无迹可寻
and those carts are too easy to buy or steal to trace.
死亡威胁查的怎么样了
How you coming on those death threats?
我们不是都说明白了吗
I thought we talked about this.
罗纳德・丹泽尔被杀了
Ronald Danzer was murdered.
抓住凶手是我们的职责
It's our job to catch murderers.
那人是个骗子
The guy was a crook.
但他还没被定罪
Who had not been convicted of any crime.
去跟那两个被他骗走一辈子积蓄
Tell that to the two guys who killed themselves
而自杀的人说去
because he lost their life savings.
这人30年来一直养尊处优
This guy was living high for 30 years
市里不单对他溜须拍马
while the city kissed his ass
还表彰他的慈善事业
and gave him awards for being such a philanthropist.
那我们就让凶手逃之夭夭吗
So we just let his killer go free.
凶手要是走进来束手就擒  我就逮捕他
Guy walks in here, holds out his hands, I'll arrest him.
否则  我就当正义已经得到伸张了
Otherwise, I'm content justice was served.
就像韦恩夫妇那样吗
Like with the Waynes? Is that what you mean?
是马里奥・佩珀杀了韦恩夫妇
Mario Pepper killed the Waynes.
我们也把佩珀正法了
We killed Pepper.
案子结了
That case is closed.
戈登警探
Detective Gordon?
我是青少年保护机构的戴维斯・拉蒙德
Davis Lamond from Juvenile Services?
你要求见塞琳娜・凯尔
You asked to see Selina Kyle.
能签下监管文件吗
Could you sign for custody?
等你完事了
And when you finish,
麻烦把她送去我们沃特街的新楼
you can bring her to our new facility on Water Street.
她明天要转移去州北
She's scheduled to be transferred upstate tomorrow.
那估计得推迟了
Yeah, that's gonna be delayed.
她有一起案件的线索
She has information about an investigation.
你能往后站一点吗
Would you mind... stepping... back... A bit, please?
等等
Wait a minute.
她是被绑架的小孩之一吗
Is that one of the kids that was snatched?
又是一个结了的案子
Another closed case.
你是不懂什么叫结案了吗
What is it about the word "closed" you don't understand?
是别的事
This is something else.
你继续读威胁信  找气球
Just read the letters, track the balloons.
我一个小时内回来
I'll be back in an hour.
好的  老大  马上去办
Yeah, boss. Get right on it.
我笔哪去了
Where's my pen?
你为什么在乎杀死韦恩夫妇的真凶是谁
So why do you care who really killed the Waynes?
因为我想见到真凶绳之以法
Because I want the person responsible brought to justice.
这句话是从书里看到的吗
Did you read that in a book or something?
还有
And...
我对那个男孩发了誓
I made a promise to the boy.
说啊
So?
凶手是从那边过来的
The killer came from there.
抢了男人的钱包  和女人的项链
Took the man's wallet and the woman's necklace.
然后开枪杀了他们俩
Then shot them both.
留了男孩一命
He left the boy alive.
我在那上面
I was up there.
所有人都知道这些
Everybody knows that much.
而且凶手蒙面了
Plus, the killer's face was covered.
一开始不是
Not at first.
他走向他们的时候才戴上面罩
He pulled up his scarf when he walked toward them.
我瞥见了
I saw him for a second.
你在黑暗之中看到他了
You saw him... here... in the dark?
我在黑暗之中也看得见
I can see in the dark.
你不信我
You don't believe me.
别说你是不是对你所看到的撒了谎
There's a question of whether you're lying about what you saw,
你当时到底在不在这儿都是个问题
and then there's the question of whether you were even here.
-你没给我证据  -我刚告诉你了
- You're not giving me proof. - I just told you,
在那之前我刚偷了一个白痴的钱包
I stole some chump's wallet just before it happened.
就离这儿两个街区
That was, like, two blocks from here.
他没报警吗
Didn't he report it?
是有个人报警说他的钱包被偷了
Yes, a man did report his wallet stolen
贼的长相跟你相符  而且没错
by a thief that matches your description, and, yes,
刚好是在韦恩夫妇被杀之前
the timing does work out to just before the Waynes were murdered.
但也不能证明你当时在这儿
But that does not place you here.
我把钱包扔了
I dumped the wallet.
在那儿
There.
下水道  好极了
The sewer. Great.
倒不是我信不过你  担心你会逃跑
It's not that I don't trust you not to run away.
但是  我确实信不过
But, well... I don't.
你找到钱包就会放我走  对吧
You find the wallet, you'll let me go, right?
-就这么定了  -不
- That's the deal. - No.
找到钱包  说明你来过
Find the wallet, that places you here.
还得去找那个人
We still have to find the guy.
太扯了
That's bull!
就这么说定了
That's the deal.
真好
Oh, great.
该死  她说的是实话
Son of a bitch. She was telling the truth.
警探先生
Oh, Detective?
你会需要这个的
You're gonna need these.
等等
Hey, wait a minute!
拉兹罗  宝贝
Lazlo, honey,
去休息吧
take a rest.
可怜的孩子
Poor thing.
哎呦
Well, well, well.
蒙托亚和艾伦警探
Detectives Montoya and Allen.
什么风把二位吹来了
To what do I owe this honor?
来看望你一下
Thought we'd pay our respects.
顺便问问你有没有看见科波特
Maybe ask if you'd seen your friend Cobblepot around.
奥斯瓦尔德
Oswald.
你这么一提  我才发觉很久没见他了
Now that you mention it, I haven't seen him.
很有意思吧
Isn't that funny?
几乎和两个重案组警探来找奥斯瓦尔德
Almost as funny as two detectives from Major Crimes
这样的小人物一样有意思
looking for a nobody like Oswald.
咱们就别绕弯子了
Can we stop the dance?
他死了  对吗
He's dead, isn't he?
因为他告诉我们
He was killed 'cause he told us
佩珀是被栽赃成了杀韦恩夫妇的凶手
about Pepper being framed for the Wayne murders.
他死了
He's dead.
但那个告密小人不是我杀的
But I didn't kill the little snitch.
听说  动手的是吉姆・戈登
Word is, Jim Gordon pulled the trigger.
你有证据吗
You have proof?
我看起来像警察吗
What do I look like, a cop?
我只是听说
I only heard
詹姆斯・戈登让可怜的奥斯瓦尔德
that James Gordon splattered poor Oswald's brains
血染哥谭河了
all over Gotham River.
戈登有什么理由杀科波特
Why would Gordon want to murder Cobblepot? Huh?
就为了不让他说出栽赃内幕吗
Just to keep him quiet about the frame?
这个问题问的不好  帅哥
Wrong question, gorgeous.
动手的是吉姆・戈登  命令是谁下的呢
Jim Gordon pulled the trigger, but who gave the order?
谁能让警察犯下冷血凶杀呢
Who could make a cop commit cold-blooded murder?
法尔科内
Falcone.
你的推理能力让我震惊
Your deductive powers astonish me.
说实话  我都有点怕了呢
Honestly, I just got a chill.
最近有流言说
You know, there's a rumor going around that
法尔科内揍了你的新男宠
Falcone gave your latest boy-toy a nasty beating.
你这样说不会是为了报复他吧
You wouldn't be looking for a little revenge, now, would you?
我只想为可怜的奥斯瓦尔德讨回公道
I just want justice for little Oswald.
科波特
Hey, Cobblepot.
你不是死了吗
Hey, you're supposed to be dead.
我想你是认错人了
I'm afraid you have me confused.
我名叫迪米特里  敖德萨来的
My name is Dimitri from Odessa.
我听说你因为告密被杀了
I-I heard you got whacked for ratting.
我把你交给菲什  她肯定会好好打赏我
Yeah, Fish is gonna pay some serious cash for your skinny ass.
不不  求你  不要
No, no, no, no! No, please!
求你  她会杀了我的
Please, please, she'll kill me!
你干吗还要回来呢
Why'd you even come back, huh? Huh?
我不能不回来  哥谭是我的家啊
I-I could not stay away. Gotham is my home!
这是我的宿命
It's my destiny!
你不知道这里将要发生什么  我知道
You don't see what's coming! I do!
哥谭需要我  我是哥谭的未来
Gotham needs me! I am its future!
如果真是这样  那哥谭可是前途堪忧了
If you're its future, then Gotham is in big trouble.
是  是啊
Yes. Yes, it is.
我要一个金枪鱼三明治  谢谢
Can I have a tuna sandwich, please?
-阿尔弗雷德  我不想玩  -怎么了
- Alfred, I don't want to do this. - What?
-住手  我不想玩  住手  -来啊  出手
- Stop. I don't want to do this. Stop. - Come on. Swat.
预备
En garde.
这就对了  怎么  怎么了
There you go, son. What? What?
-就这点本事吗  -我不要...玩这个
- Is that all you got? - I'm not... doing this.
怎么了
Uh... what?
她终于爆发了
There she blows,
眉宇间有虎的凌厉
the eye of the tiger
呼吸间都是虎的威风  布鲁斯少爷
through the wind in your nostrils, Sir Bruce,
血管里血液翻涌
the blood in his veins.
这就对了  小心头
That's it. Mind your head!
请您原谅  先生  我差点...
I do beg your pardon, sir. I'm most...
看我一击
Might be the bat.
热血沸腾了
Blood's up.
那下疼了吧  也不是
That's got to hurt. No, not really.
我让你住手
I said stop!
停  放剑
Stop. Down swords.
我投降
I surrender.
瞧
See?
一场漂亮的
A nice...
剑战能让你热血沸腾  不是吗
sword fight gets your blood up, doesn't it?
好过翻阅这些灰扑扑的旧文件
Better than reading these dusty old files.
这是什么啊
What is this, anyway?
警方的案卷
Police file.
关于你爸妈的案子  你怎么拿到的
About your mom and dad. How'd you get these?
不是太难
Wasn't-wasn't hard.
你为什么要看这些文件  这多可怕
Why would you want to look at these? They're horrible.
会让你做噩梦的
They're gonna give you nightmares.
反正我拿到了
I-I have those, anyway, and...
我在查找线索
I'm looking for clues.
你还变成侦探了
What, so you're a detective now, are you?
如果我能找到线索的话
If I find a clue I am.
那你找到线索了吗
Have you found a clue?
还没
Not yet.
Not yet?
戈登警探已经答应你
Now, Detective Gordon has promised you
他会找出杀害你父母的凶手
that he will find the person that killed your parents.
你真的相信他会吗
Do you really believe he will?
他会尽全力
He will try.
这点我可以肯定
Of that I am certain.
是的  詹姆斯・戈登警探
Yeah. Detective James Gordon.
今早你们一个顾问带了个女孩来见我
One of your counselors brought me a girl this morning,
我签了监管
and I signed for custody.
这是我正要说的
That's what I'm saying.
我不能带她回去  她逃走了
I can't bring her back. She got away.
是吗  我对此也不高兴呢
Yeah? Well, I'm not happy about it either.
烦躁不安吗  戈登
On edge, Gordon?
我很好
I'm fine.
有什么能帮你的吗
How can I help you?
我们只是想知道
We were just, uh, wondering
你开枪打爆科波特的脑袋
when you shot Cobblepot in the head
然后把他的尸体丢进河里
and dumped his body in the river,
法尔科内给你钱了吗
did Falcone pay you?
还是只算是帮阁下大人个忙呢
Or was that more of a "Favor to the Don" type thing?
不管你听到了什么  都不是真的
Whatever you heard, it's not true.
那你的意思是你没杀科波特
Oh, so you mean you didn't kill Cobblepot?
还是你不是为了法尔科内
Or you didn't do it for Falcone?
我们想给你个对我们坦白的机会
We thought we'd give you a chance to tell us the truth.
警察之间说句实话
Cop to cop.
你们没听懂我的话  我没杀他
You're not listening. I didn't kill him.
那9月17号那晚你在哪
Okay, so where were you on the night of September the 17th?
你真的要问我这个问题吗
Are you really asking me this?
重案组什么时候变成内务处了
Since when did Major Crimes become I.A.?
就在警察开始替黑帮杀人的时候
When cops started doing hits for the Mob.
是吗  那等你有真凭实据再来找我
Yeah? Well, come back to me when you have actual proof.
在此之前  别浪费我的时间
Until then, don't waste my time.
戈登  给你个建议
Hey, Gordon, piece of advice:
洗个澡
Take a shower.
你像下水道一样臭
'Cause you stink like a sewer.
任何工作都行  哪怕是洗碗工
Any job at all. Even dishwasher.
我们满员了
We're staffed up.
我只求一个证明自己的机会
I only ask a chance to prove myself.
你在餐厅里工作过吗
You ever work in a restaurant?
不算是
Not exactly...
在餐厅里要站一整天
Here, you're on your feet all day.
你穿的鞋子都不对
You don't even have the right shoes.
你在这儿啊
There you are.
气象气球工厂的老板在楼下
I got the owner of a weather balloon factory downstairs,
他说要给我们提供线索
says he's got something for us.
蒙托亚和艾伦来过
Montoya and Allen came by.
-指控我杀了科波特  -见鬼的
- Accused me of killing Cobblepot. - Damn.
-肯定是有人泄密了  -无所谓
- Somebody must've talked. - Doesn't matter.
他们来找你  就说明他们没有证据
The fact they're here means they got nothing,
他们也查不到什么
and they're gonna get nothing.
说到底  没人在乎科波特
End of the day, no one cares about Cobblepot.
因为他活该  就像罗纳德・丹泽尔
Because he deserved it. Like Ronald Danzer.
不要小题大做
Don't make this into something bigger.
你也是迫不得已
You did what you had to do.
是  他也许真就活该
And, yes, he probably did deserve it.
他是菲什的手下
He worked for Fish.
她不会雇什么好种
She doesn't employ altar boys.
那马里奥・佩珀呢  他也该死吗
What about Mario Pepper? He deserve what he got?
当然了
Hell, yes.
他就是个垃圾
He was a dirtbag.
他想开枪杀你  记得吗
He tried to shoot you, remember?
这事我们不是都说过了吗
And I thought we were done talking about this.
等杀害托马斯和玛莎・韦恩的真凶
We're done talking about this
而不是我们杀的替死鬼
when the person who actually murdered
被关进监狱
Thomas and Martha Wayne is in jail,
这事才算过去
not the person we killed for it.
我再跟你说一遍  戈登  放弃吧
For the last time, Gordon, let it go.
不然呢
Or what?
下一个被拉去码头枪决的人
Am I gonna be the next person taken out to the pier
是不是就轮到我了
to get a bullet in the head?
证人等着我们呢
The interview's waiting.
打扰一下
Pardon me.
你在街对面那家意大利餐厅工作
You work at that Italian restaurant across the way,
-是吗  -是的
- don't you? - Yeah.
你穿几码鞋
And what size are your shoes?
42码
Uh, nines.
真巧啊
What a coincidence!
我看到电视上那个气球
When I saw that balloon go up on TV,
立刻就知道那是我的
I knew it was one of mine,
我跟自己说"吉米
and I said to myself, "Jimmy boy,
你最好马上报警
you better call the cops right away,
不然他们会把责任推到你头上来"
or they'll try and pin this on you."
是你来找我们的啊
So it was you who called us.
我还以为是我搭档
And here I thought my partner had gone
想方设法找到了你
to the trouble of tracking you down.
你的气球怎么会被用来杀罗纳德・丹泽尔
How exactly was one of your balloons used to kill Ronald Danzer?
一个月前气球被我一个雇员偷走了
It was stole by my bum of an ex-employee a month ago.
他叫卡尔・斯麦克斯
Carl Smikers.
这就是招年轻人做事的后果
That's what I get for hiring a kid.
他有提过丹泽尔吗
Did he ever mention Danzer?
当然没有
Hell, no.
没想到他竟然知道丹泽尔是谁
I'm surprised he even knew who Danzer was.
他可不是什么
We ain't talking about
聪明过人的人物
one of those intellectually superior types here.
你有他地址吗
You got an address?
有  你们要是找到他
Yeah, but you find him,
看能不能把其它的给我要回来
see you can get back the others.
其它什么
The other what?
其它气球
The other balloons.
那东西一个一千呢
A grand a pop those things are.
他偷走四个
He stole four.
47块  弗兰基  我下周再来
$47? Frankie, I'm coming back next week.
给我积极点  知道不
Try to show some initiative, all right?
知道了  比尔
Okay. Bill.
你真是毒贩子的耻辱
You're a disgrace to drug dealers.
热狗
Hot dog?
滚开
Get lost.
热狗
Hot dog?
我叫你滚开
I said get lost!
克兰斯顿警督
Lieutenant Cranston?
行了
All right.
看看...
Let's see...
看你有什么
Let's see what we got here.
怎么回事
What the hell?
你是谁
Who are you?
不要啊
Oh, no.
好吧
Right.
早餐也不吃
So no breakfast then?
昨晚晚餐也没吃
And no dinner last night?
有什么打算
What's the new program?
想看看不吃东西能撑多久吗
Trying to see how long we can go without eating anything?
如果这样  我也不必
Right. If that's the case, I should save myself the trouble
费神做了
of making it.
你看这个了吗
Have you seen this?
气球人杀死腐败警察
看了  那疯子四处
Oh, yeah, yeah. That nuts going around
用气球杀人
offing people with balloons.
我有更简单的方法
I can think of easier ways to kill someone.
布鲁斯少爷  恕我
Master Bruce, forgive me for...
老生常谈  说什么"这种时候"
uttering the tired old words "in times like these,"
但在这种时候
but in times like these,
你更应该保持体力
you really need to keep your strength up.
我就是不饿
I'm just not hungry.
早上好
Morning.
谢谢
Thank you.
我本不想吵醒你
I tried not to wake you.
没事  我正好要开会
It's fine. I have a meeting.
你还好吧
You okay?
昨晚都没怎么睡觉
You hardly slept last night.
工作的事
Just work.
气球人吗
This Balloonman thing?
报纸上都这么说
That's what the paper's calling him.
还说他杀了个警察
And it says he killed a cop.
你不会有事吧
You're not in danger, are you?
不用担心我
You don't have to worry about me.
那是怎么回事
Well, what is it then?
我能看出来你有心事
I can see something's bothering you.
昨天
Yesterday,
第一个被害人  罗纳德・丹泽尔
the first victim, Ronald Danzer,
是个骗子
was a con man.
没人在意
Nobody cared.
而如今警察遇害
Now that a cop's been targeted,
调查就得到了全方位的支持
the investigation will get all the support it needs.
这不对
It's not right.
每个人都很重要  不该有分别
Everyone has to matter or nobody matters.
不然人民会失去信心
Otherwise people lose faith.
这才会出现义警
That's when you get vigilantes.
但那不是你的错
But that isn't your fault.
正相反  你给了人们信心
I mean, if anything, you're giving people faith.
是吗
Am I?
怎么说
How?
你的第一宗案子  就抓住了韦恩案凶手
Your first case, you caught the Wayne killer.
你知道那对这座城市意味着什么吗
Do you have any idea what that meant for the city?
你是个英雄
You're a hero.
我得走了
I gotta go.
你是警察又如何
Don't matter if you a cop.
你不干净  气球人就会找上你
You dirty, the Balloonman gonna get you.
哥谭为气球人疯狂
哥谭市民也该意识到
It's time the people of Gotham realize
他们要维护自己的权益
that they have to stand up for themselves.
气球人下一个该抓我的房东
Hey, Balloonman ought to get to my landlord next.
他是个无赖  他叫哈罗德・布莱...
He's a crook. And his name is Harold Bl...
棒极了  这正是
This is wonderful. This is like...
我希望今天出现的情形
my dream of how today was gonna go.
除了让警局丢脸
Besides the black eye to the department,
现在还出了个杀腐败警察的义警
now we have a vigilante who kills bad cops.
克兰斯顿没那么坏
Cranston wasn't that bad.
管他干过什么事
But whatever he was or wasn't guilty of,
克兰斯顿可是哥谭市警局的警督
Cranston was a lieutenant in the GCPD.
没人可以随便杀警察
You don't get to go around killing cops.
这两起案子调查的怎么样了
So where are you on this and the Danzer murder?
我们在找一个名叫卡尔・斯麦克斯的人
We're looking for a man named Carl Smikers.
他原本是失窃气球工厂的工人
He was an employee at the factory where the balloons were stolen.
我们派人在他的公寓外监视
We have uniforms staking out his apartment,
但他自昨晚就没回去过
but he hasn't been back there since last night.
是他干的吗
And you like him for this?
他有罪
Oh, he's guilty.
把我和他关一起  他会有罪的
Leave me in a room with him, he'll be guilty.
他肯定有联系  但我不确定他就是凶手
He's definitely connected, but I'm not sure he's the one.
他拿了气象气球
He had weather balloons!
克兰斯顿和丹泽尔都是被气象气球杀死的
Cranston and Danzer were killed with weather balloons!
他就是凶手
He's the guy!
斯麦克斯高中都没毕业
Smikers never graduated high school.
他没有一份工作超过一年
He's never held a job for more than a year,
他曾因招妓和藏毒被捕
he's got busts for soliciting, possession.
告诉她还有其它气球
Tell her about the other balloons.
什么其它气球
What other balloons?
斯麦克斯的老板说丢了四个气球
Smikers' boss mentioned that four balloons are missing.
还有两个流失在外
There are two of them still out there.
那么说还有两个目标
So two more targets?
知道可能是谁吗
We have any sense who they might be?
丹泽尔和克兰斯顿都是名人
Danzer and Cranston were both known figures,
也都出了名的腐败
and known to be dirty.
凶手不需要专业知识也能锁定他们
Killer didn't need any special knowledge to target them,
所以接下来的目标应该是
so, it's likely the next target is
腐败的公众人物
public and known to be corrupt.
总之  哥谭的所有当选官员都该待在家里
Basically, every elected official in Gotham should stay indoors.
找到他  马上
Find him. Now.
我们会的
We will.
We will?
不是说凶手是在替民除害吗
What happened to the killer doing the city a favor?
别让我觉得你真的在意
You're gonna make me think you actually care.
听着  机灵鬼  你想杀骗子金融家
Listen, smartass, you want to kill a corrupt financier,
随你
be my guest.
杀警察就是工作安全问题了
You kill a cop, it's a job safety issue.
我们需要个计划
We need a plan.
放轻松  找人我可是略知一二
Relax. One thing I do know is how to find someone.
今天晚些时候吧
Maybe later tonight.
-给你  -太好了  多谢
- Here you go. - Beautiful, baby.
拿去吧
There you go.
他告诉你什么了
What did he tell you?
没什么  我饿了而已
Nothing. I was just hungry.
听好了  你洗盘子
Here's the deal: You wash dishes,
擦地  倒垃圾
mop the floor, take out the trash.
其他时候  你就是聋子傻子瞎子
Otherwise, you're deaf, dumb and blind.
-我懂  -你不懂  但你会明白的
- I understand. - No, you don't, but you will.
这里可不像其他餐馆  你要么明白
This ain't like other places, and you'll either get it...
要么被开掉
Or I'll be fired?
可以这么说
You could say that.
你完全不需要担心
Oh, you have nothing to worry about.
我知道这是个好机会
I know that this is a great opportunity.
马罗尼阁下
Don Maroni!
见到您真高兴
Good to see you.
-最近怎样  -欢迎欢迎
- Doing good? - Welcome. Welcome.
好的
All right.
确实是个大好的机会
A great opportunity, indeed.
嫌疑犯两年前有过招妓前科
So, our suspect had a prior for soliciting two years ago, right?
我一个姑娘觉得他很面熟
So, one of my girls thought he looked familiar,
记起他喜欢膀大腰圆的类型
remembered he liked big, brawny types.
所以她给我介绍了
So, she pointed me to that pimp,
专门负责那个类型的皮条客
that guy who specialized in that.
-他记起来...  -在你修理他之后
- He remembered... - After you roughed him up a little.
他以前经常给干洗工张先生  送货上门
...that he used to do deliveries for this, uh, dry cleaner, Mr. Chang.
而且他印象最深的是
And he remembered, on top of everything else,
这家伙爱打麻将
the guy was a mahjong guy.
他曾欠华人赌博经纪人五千美元
He was into these Chinese bookies for, like, five grand.
他们让你来这儿
And they sent you here.
一个自行车信使透露
By way of some bike messengers,
这人负责南区的扒手
the guy that runs pickpockets on the south side,
还特喜欢一家锅贴店
and a pot sticker joint the guy apparently loved.
龙煲店外卖
Dragon Palace.
我们没定...
We didn't order any...
卡尔・斯麦克斯
Carl Smikers?
快跑
Run!
哥谭市警局  你被捕了
GCPD! You're under arrest!
住手  不然我就...
Stop, or I'll...
不许动
Don't move.
吉姆  能帮个忙吗
Jim, a little help!
放下
Put it down!
马上放下
Put it down now!
你把杀了奥斯瓦尔德的警察透露给重案组
You put the MCU onto that cop killing Oswald.
法尔科内如果发现是你漏的消息
Falcone finds out it came from you... I mean,
我不介意他对我做的事  只是...
I don't mind what he did to me, it's, uh...
拉兹罗  亲爱的
Lazlo, honey,
你在担心我  是吗
you're worried about me, aren't you?
但是你要记住
But you must remember,
法尔科内想伤害的不是你
it wasn't you Falcone wanted to hurt.
而是我
It was me.
明白了吗
Understand?
那孩子软了腰杆
The boy's lost his spine.
不是所有人都能经受住那种毒打
Not everyone's built for a beating like that.
罗马人近来的那个新宠
What's that new piece that the Roman's been seeing--
叫什么来着  娜塔莉亚  娜迪亚
what's her name-- Natalia? Nadia?
告诉布奇她会出意外
Tell Butch she's going to have an accident.
真是可惜
Such a shame.
她还挺漂亮的
She was a pretty girl.
顺便解决掉拉兹罗
And get rid of Lazlo while you're at it.
他太破坏气氛了
He's bringing down the mood.
我很荣幸
With pleasure.
我的天
My God!
抱歉  我敲门了  但我听到里边有人
Sorry. I knocked, but I could hear someone in here, and...
你怎么进来的
How did you get in?
我还有钥匙  记得吗
I still have a key, remember?
那你就擅自进来了
And you just let yourself in?
还给我
Give it to me.
我可以叫人逮捕你
I could have you arrested.
我也可以逮捕你
Or I could arrest you.
现在就嗑药是不是早了点
It's kind of early to get high, isn't it?
今天压力有点大
It's been a stressful day.
你就只嗑药了吗
And is that all you're doing?
是的  失望吗
Afraid so. Disappointed?
别耍我  芭芭拉
Don't play with me, Barbara.
我那时也在  记得吗
I was there, remember?
经历了全部
Through all of it.
你是说你参与其中了吧
Don't you mean you were a part of it?
好吧
Fine.
回答我的问题
Answer the question.
是的  只有这个
Yes. This is it.
你已经闯入我家
And now that you've broken into my home
指责我吸毒
and accused me of being a drug addict,
你可以走了
you can leave.
谈完戈登的事我再走
Not until we talk about Gordon.
他杀了人
He's killed a man.
你说过了  但那不是真的
You told me. It's not true.
不是马里奥・佩珀  是另一个人
Not Mario Pepper, another man.
是哥谭第一黑帮老大卡麦・法尔科内
And he killed him on the orders of Carmine Falcone,
下令让他杀的
biggest crime boss in Gotham.
你说谎
You're lying.
但是  我该习惯了
But, you know, I guess I should be used to that.
没错
True.
我们在一起时  我的确对你说过谎
When we were together, I did lie to you.
说过很多谎
A lot.
但你总是知道的
But you always knew.
你只要直视我的眼睛
You looked in my eyes,
就会知道我是否对你说谎
and you knew when I was lying to you.
我现在在说谎吗
Am I lying now?
是因为我爱他吗
Is it just because I love him?
所以你这么铁了心要毁了他
Is that why you are so determined to destroy him?
我已经戒酒一年了
I've been sober for a year.
我知道这无法抹去我的过错
Look, and I know that doesn't erase the things that I did.
但我还是在乎你的
But I still care about you.
我无法忍受你跟他在一起
I can't stand you being with this man.
你值得拥有更好的
You deserve better.
走
Leave.
马上
Now.
问他奥斯瓦尔德・科波特失踪的那晚他在哪
Ask him where he was the night that Oswald Cobblepot disappeared.
那是他杀害的人的名字
That's the name of the man he killed.
我说的是实话  我没杀那些人
I-I'm telling the truth, I didn't kill those guys.
杀警察  为什么我要杀警察
I mean, a cop?! Why would I kill a cop?!
也许因为你就是个偷东西  杀警察的垃圾
Maybe because you're a thieving, cop-murdering pile of crap.
但这还只是个理论
But, mind you, that's just a theory.
你承认你偷气球
You admit stealing the balloons.
对  那是因为我欠高利贷的钱
Yeah. Yeah, but I owed these loan sharks,
如果我不还钱  他们会切下我的...东西
and-and if I didn't pay 'em, they were gonna cut off stuff.
那么丹泽尔和克兰斯顿到底是谁杀的
So if you didn't kill Danzer and Cranston, who did?
你把气球卖给谁了
Who'd you sell the balloons to?
我没见着他的脸
I never saw his face.
我们有个交易地点  交换气球和钱
We had a drop-off point to exchange the balloons and money.
知道这什么情况吗  吉姆
You know what we got here, Jim?
这是个犯罪大师啊
We got us a criminal mastermind, hmm?
不仅凶器消失在同温层里
Not only is the murder weapon in the stratosphere,
尸体也是  简直是完美的犯罪
but so are the bodies. It's the perfect crime!
尸体会回来的
The bodies will come back.
你说什么
What are you talking about?
你们不知道气象气球的原理吗
Do you guys not know how weather balloons work?
告诉我们  天才  不然我打死你
Tell us, genius, or I'll beat it out of you.
等下  好吧
Wait, wait, wait! Okay.
气球上升  升得越高  就越冷
They-they rise up, and-and it gets colder and colder,
气球就会变脆
and the balloon gets brittle,
氦气开始膨胀
and the helium expands.
然后呢
Then what?
然后就爆了
It pops.
我真的开始讨厌这宗案子了
I'm really starting to dislike this case.
他们在哪找到的那么大的铲子
Where do you think they find shovels that big, huh?
现在我们只需要担心最后一个气球了
We only have to worry about one more balloon.
-谁  -奎恩主教
- Who? - Cardinal Quinn.
他当时在园子里沉思
He was meditating in his garden.
阿尔瓦雷斯正在赶往凶案现场
Alvarez is on his way to the scene.
这下教会也要向我们施压了  真好
Now we're gonna have the church on our back. Great.
虽然奎恩是出了名的闲混神父
Forget the fact that Quinn was known as the diddling priest.
这是我们在克兰斯顿的口袋里找到的
Here's what we found in Cranston's pockets.
没摔碎的东西
What wasn't smashed to bits.
为什么上面有你的名字  吉姆
Why's your name on this, Jim?
我知道气球人是谁了
I know who the Balloonman is.
巴蒙特餐馆
法尔科内是哥谭的老大
You see, Falcone is only the boss of Gotham
只因为人们认定他是老大
because people believe he's the boss.
所以阿卡姆会改变现状
That's what this Arkham thing is gonna change.
人们会看清皇帝新衣的真相
People are gonna see that the emperor's got no clothes.
我在白费唇舌  你个白痴
I'm wasting my breath. You're an idiot.
滚出去吧
Get out of here.
你是什么人
Who the hell are you?
我...很抱歉  先生
Uh, I-I'm sorry, sir.
-我是...  -等一下
- I'm... - Hold on.
放下
Put that down.
你刚刚在听我说话  你是新来的
You were listening, huh? You're new.
-叫什么  -帕罗  先生
- What's your name? - Paolo, sir.
意大利人吗  看着不像啊
Italian. You don't look Italian.
我母亲有意大利血统
Well, on my mother's side.
我只承认我母亲这边的亲戚
It's the side that I claim.
爱妈妈的好孩子
A boy who loves his mother.
给你  拿着吧
Here you go. Take it.
我以前也像你一样
I was a lot like you.
白手起家
Started from nothing.
但我低调做人  努力做事  看看我如今的成就
But I kept my head down, I worked hard, now look at me.
哥谭是机遇之城
Gotham is the city of opportunity.
是啊  先生  我也这样认为
Yes, sir. I believe that, too.
你刚刚听到我说的话了吗
You hear what I was saying back there?
那些名字  法尔科内  阿卡姆
Those names: Falcone, Arkham--
你知道什么意思吗
they mean anything to you?
老实说  先生  我什么都没听到
Honestly, sir... I didn't hear anything at all.
好孩子
Attaboy.
气球人再度出击
The Balloonman has struck once again.
气球人杀死神父
曾被指控犯有多起性骚扰的奎恩主教
Cardinal Quinn, accused of multiple counts of sexual abuse,
成了这位义警的新目标
is the latest victim of the vigilante.
你看  这可不好
See this... this is not good.
哪能随随便便就杀神父
You can't go around killing priests.
至少不能当众杀
At least not in public.
去照顾妈妈吧  帕罗
Got take care of your mother, Paolo.
他叫戴维斯・拉蒙德  48岁
His name is Davis Lamond; 48.
他在青少年保护机构已经干了15年了
He's worked at Juvenile Services for 15 years.
没有前科
No priors.
今天没去上班
He didn't show up for work today,
一直没回公寓
and hasn't been back to his apartment.
我们在两边都安排了警员
We have uniforms at both.
你确定就是他
And you're positive he's the killer?
我们在克兰斯顿尸体上找到一张表格
We found a form on Cranston's body
那是我昨天早上给拉蒙德的
that I'd given Lamond yesterday morning.
还有能打开拉蒙德公寓的钥匙
Also keys that opened Lamond's apartment.
我猜他们当时打了起来
I'm guessing they had a scuffle,
克兰斯顿翻了他的兜
Cranston went through his pockets,
但拉蒙德还是把他吊到气球上了
but Lamond managed to attach him to the balloon.
那拉蒙德为什么突然爆发了
So what caused Lamond to snap?
不知道
Not sure.
拉蒙德的同事都说他周到  尽心
Lamond's coworkers describe him as thoughtful, dedicated,
还有几个人说人很好
sweet-- a few said that.
好啊  是那种人很好的杀警义警呢
Oh, great, one of those sweet cop-killing vigilantes.
他最后一个目标呢
And what about his last target?
跟其他的一个规律
Same profile as all the rest.
知名
Well known.
看似受人尊敬
Seemingly respectable.
实则腐败
Actually corrupt.
这可是哥谭
This is Gotham.
这并没有缩小范围
That doesn't exactly narrow it down.
而与此同时  市长  市议会
Meanwhile, I have the mayor, city council,
半数的法官和神职人员都躲在家里
half the city's judges and clergy hiding indoors
叫嚷着让总警监找到凶徒
screaming at the commissioner to find the guy.
你猜猜总警监会冲谁嚷嚷
And guess who he screams at?
我们已经发布了他的照片
We've got his photo out there.
迟早能找到他的
It's just a matter of time.
没消息
Nothing.
是嘛
Really?
你的华人高利贷和妓女关系网毫无收获吗
Your network of Chinese loan sharks and hookers came up empty?
回头再得意吧  我们想想
Gloat later. Let's think about it.
他得存储气球
He had to store the balloons,
氦气罐  他用的推车
the helium canisters, the carts he was using...
或许他会藏在储藏设施  仓库里
Uh, maybe a storage facility. A warehouse.
或者废弃大楼
Or an abandoned building.
就这个
That's it?
你怎么想到的
How'd you come up with that?
跟我说的有什么不同
It's the same thing I just said.
你为什么觉得会是这儿
What made you figure this place?
昨天那个女孩  塞琳娜
The girl yesterday, Selina,
她说她待在新的青少年保护机构大楼
she told me she was in a new juvie building.
拉蒙德也这么说  所以我就想
Lamond, the counselor, said the same thing, so I'm thinking
老楼干什么用了
what happened to the old juvie building?
原来  市里准备要爆破掉
Turns out... city's getting ready to demo it.
即使他之前真躲在这儿  估计也早跑了
Look, even if he was here, he's probably long gone.
他只剩一个气球了
He's only got one balloon left.
也知道我们要抓到他了
He knows we're closing in.
就在那儿呢
Or that's it right there.
布洛克
Bullock!
马上放下枪
Drop the gun! Now!
不行啊  警探  我的使命还没完成
I can't do that, Detective. I'm not done yet.
我再说一遍  放下枪
Once more time: drop it.
你该帮我才对
You should be helping me.
你在浪费口舌
You're wasting your breath.
我的搭档觉得你跟你杀的那些渣滓一样坏
My partner here thinks you're as bad as the scum you kill.
而我倒觉得你是在为民除害
Me, I can see how you're kind of doing us a favor.
所以别杀我  好吗
So don't shoot me, all right?
你跟我一样相信正义
You believe as I do.
我知道是你抓到了那些绑架孩子的人
I know you're the one who caught those child snatchers.
-你为此拿性命冒险  -我也是啊
- You risked your life. - Uh, so did I.
你要保护无辜者吗
You want to protect the innocent?
是的  法律会保护无辜者
Yes. And we have laws for that.
如果执法者是克兰斯顿警督那样的人
And what good are laws when they require
法律又有什么用呢
men like your Lieutenant Cranston to implement them?
还有罗纳德・丹泽尔
And Ronald Danzer--
你真以为他会蹲监狱吗
you really think he would've ever seen the inside of a jail?
还有那个神父
Or that priest?
法律为什么不惩罚他
Why didn't the law punish him?
我把一生献给哥谭的迷失儿童
You know, I have given my life to the lost children of Gotham
因为我想改变现状
because I wanted to make a difference.
你知道我做到了什么吗  什么都没有
And you know what kind of difference I made? None.
因为管理这座城市的人
Because the people running this city
他们弱肉强食  而法律就保护他们
feed off the weak and the law protects them.
你那位市长  把孩子们抓起来
And when your mayor rounded up all those children
送去州北的监狱时
to send off to that prison upstate,
我决定不能再这么下去了
I decided "no more."
我要叫他们知道  世界上是有报应的
I would teach them there are consequences.
你倒是扪心自问  警探
So why don't you ask yourself, Detective:
你到底在为谁而战
who are you fighting for?
被黑帮收买的市长
A mayor in the Mob's pocket?
收受贿赂的警察
Cops on the take?
还是弱势者  无辜者
Or for the weak and the innocent?
你究竟是谁
Who are you, finally?
算了
Aw, forget it.
别  不要
No, no!
你干什么
What're you doing?
-感觉如何啊  -抓住他
- How do you like that? - Grab him!
感觉如何  被自己搬的石头砸到脚喽
How's it feel? You're hoisted by your own petard.
别啊  吉姆
No, Jim.
吉姆  你干什么呢
Jim, what are you doing?
吉姆  松手啊
Jim, let go.
把气球打爆啊
Shoot it! Shoot the balloon!
吉姆
Jim!
放手啊
Let go!
开枪啊
Shoot it!
放手啊
Just let go!
快开枪
Shoot it, now!
卡麦
Carmine.
真是又惊又喜
What a lovely surprise.
我们还没开门  不过为你嘛
We're not quite open, but for you...
你好啊  菲什
Hello, Fish.
就是吃晚饭路过进来看看
Just stopped by on my way to dinner.
我想确保你不会记恨我
I wanted to make sure there were no hard feelings.
怎么会呢
Never.
这才是我的好姑娘
That's my girl.
说到你的姑娘  你今晚最好是为了她
Speaking of your girl, that better be the reason
才不来找我
why you're ditching me tonight.
她叫什么来着
What's her name again?
娜迪亚
Nadia?
娜塔莉娅
Natalia.
不是的  她出了事故
And no. She had an accident.
希望不太严重
I hope nothing serious.
被人抢了
A mugging.
抢了
Mugging?!
自从韦恩夫妇被杀
Ever since the Waynes were killed,
这城市都疯了
the city has gone crazy.
希望干这事的混蛋付出生命代价
I hope the punk who did it paid with his life.
等我们找到他  他会的
He will. When we find him.
还有所有帮他的人也是
Along with anyone who helped him.
你听说马罗尼那边有什么骚动吗
Are you hearing any rumblings from Maroni's camp?
你不会觉得这事
You don't actually believe that Maroni
跟马罗尼有关吧
had something to do with it, do you?
就像你说的
Like you say:
人都疯了  疯狂对生意不利
People are acting crazy, and crazy's bad for business.
尤其我们正要展开计划
Especially with everything on the horizon.
你是指阿卡姆
You're talking about Arkham.
我以为那里关门了
I thought you had that locked up.
保持警惕
Keep your eyes open.
等等
Hold on. Hold on.
等我一下
Give me a second.
还会有其他人
There will be more
我这样的人  警探
like me, Detective.
你知道的  对吧
You know that, don't you?
如果我们尽职就不会了
Not if we do our job.
我们会的  我会的
And we will. I will.
你的机会过去了
You had your chance.
你们所有人
All of you.
你最后的目标是谁
Who was your last target?
义警气球人的复仇之旅
The crusade of the vigilante known as the Balloonman
今晚结束了  他已被警察逮捕
ended tonight when he was apprehended by police.
他是唯一抵抗
He was one man who stood up
正在腐蚀哥谭核心的腐败
to the corruption eating at the heart of Gotham,
甘愿为了拯救法律而触犯法律的人
willing to break the law in order to save it.
哥谭的罪犯今晚能睡个好觉了
Well, I imagine the criminals of Gotham are sleeping well tonight.
他杀了人
He killed people.
他也是罪犯了
That made him a criminal, too.
这话没错
That's very true.
还要别的吗
Can I get you anything else?
不用了  谢谢  阿尔弗雷德
No, thank you, Alfred.
好吧
Right, well, you know...
尽量吃一点  好吗
do try and eat a bit, won't you?
你要是也轻得飘走了就不好了
Be a shame to have you floating away.
...哥谭市警局认为这是胜利
...the GCPD claims a win,
但我不禁想问
but this journalist is left to wonder:
气球人被抓后
now that the Balloonman is gone,
谁将来守卫哥谭人民
who will defend the people of Gotham?
您收看的是7频道7点新闻
This is Channel 7 at 7:00, reporting live
从市中心前哥谭青少年保护机构大楼发来的现场报道
from the former Gotham juvenile facility center in downtown,
给您带来最新的消息
with your minute-to-minute updates.
回到新闻直播间  约翰
Back to the newsroom, John.
你没事
You're okay.
你没事吧
Are you okay?
嗯
Yeah.
我只是摔了一下  没事的
I fell is all. I'm fine.
到底怎么了
What's wrong?
我希望你知道
I want you to know
你什么都可以跟我说
that you can tell me anything.
这座城市病了
The city's sick.
我之前并没有意识到
Sick in a way I hadn't realized.
他们把他带走的时候
When they were taking him away,
那个气球人杀手
this Balloonman killer,
我问他最后的目标是谁
I asked who his last target was.
你知道他说什么吗
You know what he said?
无所谓了
Doesn't matter.
他是说  市长  法官
He meant the mayor, judges,
任何位高权重的人
anyone in a position of power--
他们都有罪
they're all guilty.
不是这样的
But that's not true.
至少他是这么想
It's how he feels.
他们都是这么想
It's how they all feel.
每个人
Everyone.
所以市民那么喜欢他
That's why the city embraced him.
因为我们让他们失望了
Because we let them down.
但如果大家都私设公堂
But if people take the law into their own hands,
那法律就形同虚设
then there is no law.
我们就完了
And we're lost.
有警察也那么做
There are cops who do it.
做他做的那种事
The same thing he did.
但你不会的
But you never would.
你觉得我做得出吗
Do you think I could?
不
No.
我了解你
I know you,
吉姆・戈登
Jim Gordon.
我爱你
And I love you.
我去给你拿杯酒
And now I'm gonna get you a drink.
我开吧
I'll get it.
吉姆
Jim.
你好啊  詹姆斯
Hello, James.
老朋友
Old friend.
如需其它字幕  请登陆新浪微博[WEB&BD版美剧字幕精编者]
或发邮件 lj20090303@163.com